sorcery protect the charitable here
巫术保护这里的慈善机构
the conference d8 conference party band no
会议D8会议派对乐队编号
Mappu's biggest talking to problem could be
马普对问题的最大讨论可能是
my name is leif gunkel system
我的名字叫莱夫·甘克尔系统
hamburg work in the host software
汉堡在主机软件中工作
development the head of the web
开发网络负责人
engineering department
工程部
ok to do this short introduction to test
可以做这个简短的介绍来测试
fruits that you like modern heads up
你喜欢现代的水果
talking about is over
谈论结束了
[Music]
[音乐]
new system hotel components or test
新系统的酒店组件或测试
access system comes to it
进入系统
shootout
枪战
because the costs continue there
因为费用在那里继续
[Music]
[音乐]
only when we offer building services
只有在我们提供建筑服务时
The unit raises the trust for business unit
部门对业务部门的信任
logic design test set the seas on
逻辑设计测试开始了
racing operation of the skies of education
赛车教育的天空
test unit is ok and service test anyway
测试单元还可以，并且仍然可以进行服务测试
sony directly also came that you like
索尼也直接来了，你喜欢
hetzerath bhf capital services publi the
hetzerath bhf Capital Services publi
mouse the siesta software from endpoint
从端点上单击午睡软件
access tripoli ostring to character
将tripoli ostring访问角色
the two the and performance business
两者兼而有之
it's her here
是她在这里
how could sap here an extremely phase
怎么会在这里闷闷不乐
one to one time from frog smedley saturday
从青蛙史沫特莱星期六到一对一
[Music]
[音乐]
convenience message is from string thing
便利信息来自字符串
how ok so we can use user business logic
好的，这样我们就可以使用用户业务逻辑
1 2 it's so incredibly almost
1 2它几乎是令人难以置信的
wait 14 bit more like it's okay the
再等14点就可以了
performance and the expected ok expected
性能和预期还可以
results should you be business
结果你应该做生意
logic systems christian point okay for that
逻辑系统克里斯汀点还可以
were they are they as short as they are
他们是不是像他们一样矮
the share of community health service
社区卫生服务的份额
pack
包
also in tobias welz test for
也在tobias welz测试中
service access jump test sst the haft
服务访问跳转测试系统
The port designs the rest of the template
端口设计其余模板
you get discovered and then you can then
你被发现，然后你就可以
here at the end of the convenience trade fair because of it
因为它，这里在便利贸易展览会结束时
very okay very relaxed Horst added
非常好，非常放松，Horst添加了
port wiegard from the service some text
从服务端口维加德一些文本
the console playstation yes something like 1000
控制台Playstation是1000
cordial service sector berlin as in
柏林的热情服务部门
mauth cases under review of expectations
正在审查期望的mauth案例
advertising system adsense fierce penaltys der
广告系统adsense激烈的罚款
to look into another way of
研究另一种方式
doing test sets young people
做测试集年轻人
here transformed watched introduction
这里转变了观看的介绍
to patients base and doc actually a lot
对患者基础和医生来说实际上很多
about how great sports sl like kuwait
关于科威特的体育运动史
plugin supports out using docr for
插件支持将docr用于
integration service controller
集成服务控制器
the user at private first calls the
私人用户首先致电
take last
最后
finally no first for users will be there
最终没有用户第一
iwf annika sander is said to be in kassandra
据说iwf annika sander在kassandra
conference on the way you can
以您可以的方式召开会议
something you should know about is the
你应该知道的是
special forces against henning
反对亨宁的特种部队
update-server what the conficker servers are
更新服务器什么是配置服务器
otto complements st
奥托补充st
so now accept the world to do so often
所以现在要接受世界经常这样做
Paris is not the light products
巴黎不是轻产品
cassandra angel spotify has been prepared
cassandra天使spotify已准备好
will realize that the jus kassandra
会意识到，jus kassandra
Pretests relaxed stripped down to side
预测试放松下来
starts july almost blinded external
7月开始几乎外部蒙蔽
burden
负担
Ok so that's how she gets here as he dr
好吧，那是她博士来的时候
compost case a jogger compost case like
堆肥箱
the booklet definition so kassandra in
小册子的定义，所以卡桑德拉在
politics col kassandra export import
政治上校卡桑德拉出口进口
kassandra typical uses 6 supplemented by
卡桑德拉典型用途6辅以
sting but spectators demanded is great
刺痛，但观众要求的很棒
like never and next three days for user
永远不会，用户接下来的三天
develop survey enhanced kassandra
开发调查增强的卡桑德拉
if the mountains are four, basically
如果山是四，基本上
the mdr compost case if we like little
如果我们不喜欢的话，请在堆肥堆肥的情况下
great if that says local compost plugins
如果那说本地堆肥插件很棒
provided by other stewart and katharina
由其他stewart和katharina提供
full cup of tea set up the last four for
倒满四杯茶
spring break
春假
local service call kassandra guesthouse
本地服务电话卡桑德拉旅馆
informations so the the ip port and
信息，因此IP端口和
give it to the environment of service
提供给服务环境
that they give the information built
他们给建立的信息
the penaltys internal service
内部处罚服务
okay that's just a few lines and now
好吧，现在只有几行
taxes fire us from the poolside us
税收把我们从池畔解雇了
Congress save food when and how can
国会何时何地可以节省食物
she is now extremely the computer pollman
她现在是极端的计算机民意调查员
like you know this application to say
就像你知道这个应用要说的
i'm off to samsung story station
我要去三星故事站
to the wall clock herbert comfortable
挂钟赫伯特舒适
apothecary's day little thing called postman
药剂师节的小东西叫邮递员
there are posts
有帖子
ok now i red i temperature that doesnt matter how
好吧，现在我红了，我的温度没关系
circle complements my friend is that the
圈子补充了我的朋友是
community you are like them here
社区，你就像他们在这里
michael collins this service to
迈克尔·柯林斯这项服务
produce and purchasing and body the
生产和采购及车身
colleague holger the user side
同事holger用户端
the report is the enemies to 1100's
报告是1100的敌人
Wake up station as Hemingway Kassandra will
像海明威·卡桑德拉（Hemingway Kassandra）一样唤醒车站
the bugginger services airways ana like
Bugginger服务的航线全都像
the bathers can ternitz
沐浴者可以坐下
live streaming continent you do not have
您没有的实时流媒体大陆
thought you do not have to set up
以为您不必设置
rostocker compost the penaltys and you
罗斯托克堆肥的罚款和你
find your are the world 'at ssm and
在ssm中找到您的世界，
check24 hotel the ring is a tumor
check24酒店的戒指是肿瘤
user wants to have something
用户想要一些东西
people with the same eyes
眼睛相同的人
Ackerschott la stampa from mainz is
美因茨的Ackerschott la stampa是
okay something like no jetset like
好吧，就像没有喷气式飞机一样
actually getting a to i hear that we
实际上我知道我们
get it's okay
没关系
Stephanie's party is exactly kassandra again
斯蒂芬妮的派对又是卡桑德拉
inspiration test data warehouse so the
灵感测试数据仓库
coast meet
海岸聚会
the fei nations and find out can
菲国家，并找出可以
so what you know i stop service here
所以你知道我在这里停止服务
will be off automatically
将自动关闭
stocker container right in it but in
在其中的储货容器
almost for you want to take the im
几乎是因为您想接受即时消息
container like the quartet and tested
像四重奏一样经过测试的容器
the output and one only smile
输出和唯一的微笑
service as well as conecon lines they know
服务以及他们知道的锥线
just right in the statement summer season
就在声明的夏季
a user test interest so
用户测试兴趣，因此
[Music]
[音乐]
she should be specialized under table here
她应该在桌子底下专长
and now be used in just four days
现在只需四天即可使用
to connect to the half in the 2
连接到2的一半
[Music]
[音乐]
roger the climate like cleaning data advises
像清洁数据建议的那样使气候更恶劣
expert of tech suits becomes call it
技术套装专家称呼它
like it is user kassandra okay if you
就像是用户kassandra好的，如果您
It's just like come back to the
就像回到
integration and here is something that
整合，这就是
more expensive using this kassandra as well
用这个卡桑德拉也更贵
have some tests here as effective
在这里进行一些测试是有效的
Award threat of safety car
安全车奖励威胁
reseller server like the enemies out like
转售服务器就像敌人一样
the enemies in glue travel and here we
胶水中的敌人旅行，在这里我们
no speak
不说话
colleague franz becker which motto be
同事弗朗茨·贝克尔的座右铭是
Part of the state of affairs like they are
像他们这样的状态的一部分
Do not want to get together to check at the get
不想聚在一起检查
dataram expecting sensation test okay
dataram期待感觉测试还可以
OK
行
a selling point how can so out
一个卖点怎么能这样
here was the usa back maybe explained
这是美国回来也许解释了
Paul will
保罗将
new services more user service to mac
新服务Mac的更多用户服务
app stores and know i wanna have the ins
应用程序商店，知道我想拥有ins
world of my cluster and the outside
我的集群和外界的世界
world open class the time out volt
世界公开课超时电压
connect communicate with it service
连接与其通信服务
foundry ok as well as have something you know
铸造厂还可以，并且有一些您知道的东西
the design patterns colt gateway bff
设计模式柯尔特网关bff
basin in front
前面的盆
ok so will the basic i have your say
好吧，基本我会说
pound to the timeout wanted the work is
想要超时是要工作
said to be so services okay so what we
据说服务很好，所以我们
have here is the first thing we are
这里是我们第一件事
going to your dog images of service
去你的狗服务的形象
They are the rule of thumb
他们是经验法则
a using the services what you have
使用您所拥有的服务
to do is you have the dog the offspring
要做的就是让你的狗成为后代
bot plug in will be the things in
机器人插件将是
java application plug in marsdorf
java应用程序插件marsdorf
cheering the idea configured jumps
欢呼配置跳跃的想法
the application got its user from july
该应用程序从7月获得了它的用户
plug in is
插入是
transporter really great docr plugin that
转运真的很棒的docr插件
exactly what you want to do is easy to
正是您想要做的很容易
use any and coachee luca dotti here the
在这里使用任何和受训者luca dotti
be fine group of users to say okay
可以说是好的用户群体
ssj college domain and first group
ssj大学领域和第一组
be services when half
当一半时服务
Stock market trainer we have
我们拥有的股票市场培训师
Application called that i can actually
应用程序称我实际上可以
wind gap from the fall of this fall immediately
从这个秋天的秋天开始的风隙
porsche-boss very much like how can the
保时捷老板非常喜欢
Fed on-site services company
美联储上门服务公司
keynote speaker dr
主旨演讲人博士
ok just gone to do it yourself
好的，只是自己去做
everything as the state building the
作为国家建设的一切
document services
文件服务
Almost everything depends on the account of Berlin
几乎一切都取决于柏林的账目
daughter container
子容器
it is the user first exit langau sz
这是用户第一次退出langau sz
sabrina sandra naujoks project junior
萨布丽娜·桑德拉·诺约克斯（Sabrina Sandra naujoks）初级
cluster josef the situation of jubilation
聚集约瑟夫的喜庆情况
brand certain version of your service
品牌特定版本的服务
so much in front of the small service center
小型服务中心前面有很多东西
controller and wii controller this is ex
控制器和Wii控制器，这是前
the speedway the user a first for
用户先行的高速路
users like to leave chapter
用户喜欢离开本章
okay okay
好吧好吧
[Music]
[音乐]
jogger compost creative solutions and
慢跑堆肥创意解决方案和
services if watching to you what
服务，如果看着你
you see here double compost single images
你在这里看到双堆肥单一图像
bed of the sliders more the fuel kassandra
滑块床更多的燃料卡桑德拉
the setup kiev the user service attacks
设置基辅用户服务攻击
on Kassandra in front of the user service the
在用户服务前面的Kassandra上
post information space bigger the
发布信息空间更大
join in the money from the outside and the
从外面和外面加入钱
house and port said and the capital
房屋和港口称与首都
services from ok such a mad ossi
好的服务，例如疯狂的ossi
services and day they come up exactly like
服务和他们出现的日子完全一样
the situation is as extreme as her
情况和她一样极端
bff applications to bring the rocker
bff带来摇杆的应用
images and connect
图像并连接
[Music]
[音乐]
the first such as last and sciences and
第一，例如最后和科学，
said we came here reset to users the
说我们来这里重置给用户
expected otherwise hearty double
期望否则丰盛的双
compost case kassandra value test data
堆肥箱卡桑德拉值测试数据
center let's move the back and we play
中心，让我们向后移动，我们玩
what you get back is the concert is
你回来的是音乐会
usually a my name is okay with capital
通常我的名字可以大写
so here it is easy to use this
所以在这里很容易使用
entry skeleton many rallye natural
入门骨架许多拉力赛自然
actually it's not even klose news
实际上，这甚至不是新闻
embedded database or kafka whatever my
嵌入式数据库或kafka，无论我的
first edition sold out and intended to be sold in
第一版售罄，打算在
his north station dance videos from
他的北站舞蹈视频来自
youtube
YouTube的
[Music]
[音乐]
be a separate from the test you can
与测试分开可以
get into the mainstream today so what i
今天进入主流，所以我
did it my life products for sure we
确实做到了我的生活产品吗
Thought that date is the reserve biggs
以为日期是储备金
is and its just just taken into
是，它刚刚被纳入
you responsibility offered moscow stayed away
您提供的责任莫斯科远离了
so the jusos and ju for example
所以举个例子
Cassandra
卡桑德拉
because just have one kassandra cluster
因为只有一个卡桑德拉集群
are scaling with skylink waldgirmes of the
正在与Skylink waldgirmes合作
months so the mean prostate
几个月，所以平均前列腺
test data room services
测试资料室服务
testcenters integrated into orbit smile
测试中心整合到轨道微笑中
often tasting if you really made to
经常品尝，如果你真的做了
calculate saturday sometimes in her
有时在她计算星期六
business logic ii fierce station because
业务逻辑二激烈的站，因为
what went down said you only as of
下来的话只说你
developer is busy or expect ins
开发人员很忙或期望
all of your table ok translated first
您的所有表格都可以先翻译
person am okay
人很好
[Applause]
[鼓掌]